In that case, why don't the three of us run off somewhere together?
We can't. They'd use their damn scouts and be able to track us down in no time.
Bardock? Why are you going through so much trouble?
It's not like a sane man to worry about his children. So what's gotten into you?
I don't know. Maybe it's because I'm constantly fighting, destroying,
and I'd actually like to save something from once. Especially someone who is judged to be a
lower-class warrior, like my Kakarot.
I've programmed this to head to a distant planet called Earth. The people in that world have low
power levels and aren't technologically advanced. I think you'll be able to do well there, Gene.
Good thing is, it's not an extremely valuable world, so I'm hoping it won't even show up on
the Frieza Force's radar. If your father is wrong about this, then we'll come and get you immediately.
Listen, son. You do what it takes to survive, got it?
We'll see you really soon!
Goodbye.
Don't forget us, Kakarot!